A Guide to the Agricultural Development Council records, Record Group 2 FA1440
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Research and Training Network (RTN), 1971-1983; 11; 34.09 Cubic Feet 78 containers
  - General - ADC (Box 182, Folder 3)
  - General - A (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - General - B (Box 183, Folder 2)
  - Agency for International Development (AID) (Box 183, Folder 3)
  - General - C (Box 184, Folder 1)
  - Conference Sites (Box 184, Folder 2)
  - Cooperatives (Box 184, Folder 3)
  - General - D (Box 184, Folder 4)
  - General - Dantwala (Box 185, Folder 1)
  - General - E (Box 185, Folder 2)
  - Educational Development (Box 185, Folder 3)
  - Workshop to Review and Evaluate Training of Agricultural Economists, AAEA, Kellogg Center, East Lansing, MI, 1979 June 5-6 (Box 185, Folder 4)
  - Asia Society Workshop on Time Budget Data, 1978 September 15 (Box 186, Folder 1)
  - Council on Foreign Relations - Discussions on U. S. Food and Agricultural Policy Meetings, 1978 October 5-1979 March 20 (Box 186, Folder 2)
  - Workshop on Agricultural Technology Testing, CIAT-Steppler, 1979 March 19-21 (Box 186, Folder 3)
  - Implementation of U. S. Food Aid - Title III, RTN Seminar, Princeton, NJ, 1979 January 15-16 (Box 187, Folder 1)
  - Rural Production, Employment Problems and Sex Differentiation of Wage Rates and Productive Work Opportunities, Yale University, 1978 July 11 (Box 187, Folder 2)
  - Conference on the Communication Responsibilities of the International Agricultural Research Centers (IARCs), IRRI, Los Banos, Philippines, 1979 May 14-19 (Box 188, Folder 1)
  - LDC Food Security: The International Response, Reston, VA, 1978 August 10-11 (Box 188, Folder 2)
  - Coastal Zone Management Workshop Meeting, Bangkok, Thailand, 1978 December 18-20 (Box 189, Folder 1)
  - Ladejinsky Seminar, 1975-1980 (Box 189, Folder 2)
  - Ladejinsky Legacy, 1977-1980 (Box 189, Folder 3)
  - Ladejinsky Legacy (Box 190, Folder 1-2)
  - Workshop - Room to Maneuver, Ed Clay, IDS, Sussex, 1980 December 17-19 (Box 190, Folder 3)
  - Seminar - Importance of Bypassed Areas in Asian Economic Development, Okinawa, 1981 June 15-19 (Box 191, Folder 1)
  - Marketing Workshop - Food System Organization Problems in Developing Countries, Michigan State University, 1981 January 21-23 (Box 191, Folder 2)
  - Conference - Improving the Developmental Effectiveness of Food Aid, Sri Lanka, 1980 August 18-20 (Box 192, Folder 1)
  - Seminar - Mobilizing Local Resources for Irrigation, Colombo, Sri Lanka, 1980 August 11-15 (Box 193, Folder 1)
  - Workshop on Rural Sector Management, New York, 1980 June 3 (Box 193, Folder 2)
  - Seminar on the Mechanization of Small-Scale Farming, Sapporo, Japan, 1980 July 17-19 (Box 194, Folder 1)
  - Adjustment Processes in Rural Labor Markets, Hyderabad, India, 1979 August 22-24 (Box 194, Folder 2)
  - Adjustment Processes in Rural Labor Markets, Hyderabad, India, 1979 August 22-24 (Box 195, Folder 1)
  - General - P (Box 195, Folder 2)
  - IRRI Conference and Small Farm Mechanization Conference - Photographs, 1979 May; 1980 July (Box 195, Folder 3)
  - RTN Photographs of Seminars and Workshops (Box 196, Folder 1)
  - General - Public Sector, 1971-1973 (Box 196, Folder 2)
  - General - R, 1974-1982 (Box 196, Folder 3)
  - General - Retzlaff (Box 196, Folder 4)
  - Rockefeller Foundation, 1977-1980 (Box 197, Folder 1)
  - General - RTN (Box 197, Folder 2)
  - Publications - Future, Serving Agriculture as an Administrator, Mosher (Box 197, Folder 3)
  - General - RTN Schedule of Workshops and Seminars, 1971 January-1974 May (Box 197, Folder 4)
  - Rural Credit (Box 197, Folder 5)
  - Ruttan, Vernon (Box 198, Folder 1)
  - General - S (Box 198, Folder 2-3)
  - Silverstone, Jonathan (Box 198, Folder 4)
  - General - Stevenson, A. R. (Box 198, Folder 5)
  - General - Swenson (Box 199, Folder 1)
  - General - T (Box 199, Folder 2)
  - Travers, Lee (Box 199, Folder 3)
  - General - Taylor (Box 199, Folder 4)
  - General - U (Box 199, Folder 5)
  - General - V (Box 199, Folder 6)
  - General - W (Box 200, Folder 1)
  - Walker, Thomas C. (Box 200, Folder 2)
  - General - Ben White (Box 200, Folder 3)
  - The World Bank, 1978-1979 (Box 200, Folder 4)
  - World Hunger, 1978-1979 (Box 200, Folder 5)
  - General - X, Y, Z (Box 200, Folder 6)
  - Reprints (Box 200, Folder 7)
  - General - Evenson (Box 201, Folder 1)
  - General - F (Box 201, Folder 2)
  - General - FAO (Box 201, Folder 3)
  - General - Ford Foundation, 1976-1982 (Box 201, Folder 4)
  - General - G (Box 201, Folder 5)
  - Gerard J. Gill (Box 201, Folder 6)
  - General - H (Box 202, Folder 1)
  - W. David Hopper (Box 202, Folder 2)
  - General - I (Box 202, Folder 3)
  - IAESTE, 1978 (Box 202, Folder 4)
  - International Center for Agricultural Research in the Dry Areas (ICARDA), 1978-1979 (Box 202, Folder 5)
  - International Committee on the Management of Population Programs (ICOMP) (Box 203, Folder 1)
  - General - ICRISAT (Box 203, Folder 2)
  - International Center for Research on Women (ICRW), Washington, D. C., 1980-1981 (Box 203, Folder 3)
  - Indian Institute of Management (IIMA) (Box 203, Folder 4)
  - International Development Research Centre (IDRC), 1973-1982 (Box 203, Folder 5)
  - General - India, 1977-1978 (Box 203, Folder 6)
  - International Food Policy Research Institute (IFPRI), 1978-1981 (Box 203, Folder 7)
  - International Rice Research Institute (IRRI) (Box 204, Folder 1)
  - General - J (Box 204, Folder 2)
  - Japan, 1975-1980 (Box 204, Folder 3)
  - General - Kearl, Bryant E. (Box 204, Folder 4)
  - General - K (Box 205, Folder 1)
  - General - L (Box 205, Folder 2)
  - General - M (Box 205, Folder 3)
  - General - N (Box 205, Folder 4)
  - General - O, 1975-1981 (Box 206, Folder 1)
  - General - ONG, 1976-1979 (Box 206, Folder 2)
  - Overseas Development Institute (ODI), 1978-1982 (Box 206, Folder 3)
  - RTN - A. M. Weisblat Reports (Box 206, Folder 4)
  - RTN - Workshop Reports, No. 1 and 2, 1973 (Box 206, Folder 5)
  - RTN - Seminar Reports, 1973-1975 (Box 207, Folder 1-2)
  - RTN - Newsletters, No. 1-8, 1971-1976 (Box 208, Folder 1)
  - RTN Program - General Correspondence, 1972-1976 (Box 208, Folder 2)
  - Subscription - ADC Offers Publications Series (Box 208, Folder 3)
  - RTN - New Seminiar Report Cover, 1981 January (Box 209, Folder 1)
  - Staff Paper - S. Ong - Impact of Urbanization on the Environment - A Case Study of Bangkok (Not Published) (Box 209, Folder 2)
  - RTN - Workshop Reprints and Seminar Reports (Box 209, Folder 3)
  - Seminar Papers - Food for Peace, 1979 (Box 209, Folder 4)
  - Seminar Papers - Linkage of Agriculture and Education (Box 210, Folder 1)
  - Seminar Papers - The Experience and Potential for Group Farming in Asia, Singapore, 1977 August 21-24 (Box 210, Folder 2-3)
  - Seminar Papers - Household Studies Workshop, Singapore, 1976 August 3-7 (Box 210, Folder 4)
  - Seminar Papers - Household Studies Workshop, Singapore, 1976 August 3-7 (Box 211, Folder 1-3)
  - Seminar Papers - Implementation of U. S. Food Aid, 1979 January 15-16 (Box 211, Folder 4)
  - Seminar Papers - Food System Organization Problems in Developing Countries, 1981 January 21-23 (Box 211, Folder 5)
  - Seminar Papers - The U. S. University Role in Education for Marine Resources Development in the LDC's, University of Rhode Island, 1977 November 30-December 2 (Box 212, Folder 1-2)
  - Seminar Papers - Food System Organization Problems in Developing Countries, 1981 January 21-23 (Box 212, Folder 3)
  - Seminar Papers - The Ladejinsky Legacy, Kyoto, Japan, 1977 October 10-12 (Box 212, Folder 4-5)
  - Seminar Papers - Communication Responsibilities of the International Agricultural Research Centers, 1979 May 14-19 (Box 213, Folder 1)
  - Seminar Papers - Household Studies Workshop, Singapore, 1976 August 3-7 (Box 213, Folder 2-3)
  - Seminar Papers - LDC Food Security - The International Response, Reston, VA, 1978 August 10-11 (Box 213, Folder 4)
  - Seminar Papers - Rural Finance Research (Box 214, Folder 1-3)
  - Seminar Papers - Rural Financial Markets and Institutions Workshop, Wye College, Wye, England, 1979 June 12-14 (Box 214, Folder 4)
  - Seminar Papers - Rural Financial Markets and Institutions Workshop, Wye College, Wye, England, 1979 June 12-14 (Box 215, Folder 1)
  - Seminar Papers - Farm Management Teaching Workshop, Kellogg Center, Michigan State University, East Lansing, MI, 1977 April 14-15 (Box 215, Folder 2-4)
  - Seminar Papers - Mobilizing Local Resources for Irrigation, Colombo, Sri Lanka, 1980 August 11-15 (Box 216, Folder 1)
  - Seminar Papers - Review and Evaluate Graduate Training of Agricultural Economists, Kellogg Center, Michigan State University, East Lansing, MI, 1979 June 5-6 (Box 216, Folder 2-3)
  - Seminar Papers - Resource Use and Management in the Coastal Zones of the Asian Humid Tropics, Bangkok, Thailand, 1978 December (Box 216, Folder 4)
  - Seminar Papers - Resource Use and Management in the Coastal Zones of the Asian Humid Tropics, Bangkok, Thailand, 1978 December (Box 217, Folder 1-2)
  - RTN Committee Meetings, 1971; 1978; 1979 (Box 217, Folder 3)
  - RTN Program - General Correspondence, 1977-1980 (Box 218, Folder 1)
  - Ford Foundation - Pakistan, 1973-1974 (Box 218, Folder 2)
  - Amir Muhammed, 1973 (Box 218, Folder 3)
  - ADC - Trip Reports - Pakistan, 1975-1981 (Box 218, Folder 4)
  - Ford Foundation - Pakistan - Grant Requests 1980, 1981, 1982, 1980-1982 (Box 218, Folder 5)
  - Ford Foundation - Pakistan 1978 (Box 219, Folder 1)
  - Ford Foundation - Pakistan - Grant Letter 1980-1981 (Box 219, Folder 2)
  - Ford Foudation - Pakistan - Government and University Agreements (Box 219, Folder 3)
  - Pakistan (Box 219, Folder 4)
  - Ford Foundation - Pakistan, 1975-1976 (Box 219, Folder 5)
  - Ford Foundation - Pakistan - Correspondence, 1977 (Box 219, Folder 6)
  - Ford Foundation - Pakistan - Reports, 1977-1979 (Box 219, Folder 7)
  - Ford Foundation - Pakistan - Grant Letter 1977-1979 (Box 219, Folder 8)
  - Total PERI Grant (Box 219, Folder 9)
  - Dilawar Ali Khan Travel Grant (Box 219, Folder 10)
  - PERI Staff Training, 1981-1983 (Box 219, Folder 11)
  - Muhammad Naeem AIR Training Program, Pakistan Program (Box 219, Folder 12)
  - Library Development - PERI (Box 219, Folder 13)
  - Research Internship Program - PERI (Box 219, Folder 14)
  - Economics of Village Livestock Workshop, Lahore, 1981 May 16 (Box 220, Folder 1)
  - Pakistan Journal of Ag. Econ. And Rural Soc. (Box 220, Folder 2)
  - Problems of Hill Farming in Nepal, Kathmandu, 1981 March 30-April 3 (Box 220, Folder 3)
  - Univ. of Agriculture, Faisalabad, Employment and Income of Labor, Qamar Mohy-ud-Din (Box 220, Folder 4)
  - Intercrop Economics: Cotton and Rice, Mian Aslam, Faisalabad University (Box 220, Folder 5)
  - Economic Analysis Studies - Punjab Economic Research Institute, 1983 (Box 220, Folder 6)
  - East-West Center, 1982 (Box 220, Folder 7)
  - RTN Irrigation Meeting (Box 220, Folder 8)
  - RTN Irrigation Meeting, 1979 October 24 (Box 220, Folder 9)
  - Irrigation -Making It Useful for Disadvantaged Groups Workshop, Salisbury, CT, 1980 June 19-20 (Box 220, Folder 10)
  - Reports by Marcus Franda, 1979-1980 (Box 220, Folder 11)
  - Irrigation -Making It Useful for Disadvantaged Groups Workshop, Salisbury, CT - Expenditures, 1980 June 19-20 (Box 220, Folder 12)
  - Irrigation -Making It Useful for Disadvantaged Groups Workshop, Salisbury, CT - Ford Foundation - Background, 1980 June 19-20 (Box 221, Folder 1)
  - Report to AID - Uses of Irrigation Water (Box 221, Folder 2)
  - Research Associate - Bob Yoder, 1981-1982 (Box 221, Folder 3)
  - Expenditures - Barbara Jones, S.7.15A, 1981 (Box 221, Folder 4)
  - AID contract (for researchers), 1981 (Box 221, Folder 5)
  - AID Contract (Box 221, Folder 6)
  - Private-Public Work Group, 1983 (Box 221, Folder 7)
  - ADC-IRRI Workshop Papers, 1976 (Box 222, Folder 1)
  - AID-RTN Review Committee - Report, 1977-1979 (Box 222, Folder 2)
  - Food and Fuel Seminar, 1980 (Box 223, Folder 1)
  - RTN - Natural Resources (Box 223, Folder 2)
  - Seminar - Comparative Analysis of Rural Development in China and India (Box 223, Folder 3)
  - Seminar - Agricultural Household Models: Some Extensions and Applications, World Bank, 1982 (Box 223, Folder 4)
  - RTN Program Committee Meeting, 1979 October (Box 223, Folder 5)
  - AID-RTN Review Committee - Report, 1977 May 1-1979 March 30 (Box 223, Folder 6)
  - RTN - General Expenditures, 1977-1979 (Box 224, Folder 1)
  - Administration - AID-csd 2813 - contract (Box 224, Folder 2)
  - Administration - AID-csd 2813 - reimbursements (Box 224, Folder 3)
  - Irrigation for Non-Agricultural Purposes - Fourth World Congress on Water Resources, 1981-1982 (Box 224, Folder 4)
  - RTN - Expenditures and Proposed Budgets, 1978-1981 (Box 225, Folder 1)
  - RTN-AID Contract 1978-1980 - AID-DSAN-C-0015, Project 931-0887 (Box 225, Folder 2)
  - Irrigation for Non-Agricultural Purposes - RTN Reporting Sessions, 1981 June 25; June 30 1981 (Box 225, Folder 3)
  - Planning Session on Water Use and Management, 1980 October 23 (Box 226, Folder 1)
  - Family Labor Force - ICRISAT, 1976 February 2-3 (Box 226, Folder 2)
  - Changing Role of Women in Rural Societies, Poland (Castillo), 1976 August 9-13 (Box 226, Folder 3)
  - Rural Production, Employment, 1978 February (Box 226, Folder 4)
  - Women and Development - Wellesley College, 1976 June 2-6 (Box 227, Folder 1)
  - Planning Session - Application of household time allocation studies to policy issues, 1977 October 21-22 (Box 227, Folder 2)
  - Role of Women in Rural Development, Princeton, NJ, 1974 (Box 227, Folder 3)
  - Role of Women in Rural Development, Princeton, NJ, 1974 (Box 228, Folder 1-2)
  - Evaluation of the Research and Training Network (RTN) of the Agricultural Development Council, 1977 June (Box 228, Folder 3)
  - Future Seminars, 1978-1981 (Box 229, Folder 1-3)
  - Seminar on Food Policy - Africa, 1981 August 24-26 (Box 230, Folder 1-2)
  - RTN Seminar - Implication of Small-Scale Farm Mechanization, Hangzhou, China, 1982 June (Box 230, Folder 3)
  - RTN Session - IAAEA Meeting - Jakarta 1982 - The Role of Women in the Generation of National Product: Productivity and Production in Developing Nations - Ford Foundation Grant (Box 231, Folder 1-2)
  - RTN Funding, 1980s (Box 231, Folder 3)
  - ADC - Economic Affairs Division - Agreement (and other Agreements), 1970s-1980 (Box 231, Folder 4)
- Publication Files and Papers, 1970-1982; 12; 5.79 Cubic Feet 14 letter document boxes and 1 legal box
  - Agricultural Development Council, Inc. Volume XX - Annual Reports 1977-1978, 1979 - Newsletters - Seminar Reports - Reprints, 1977-1979 (Box 232, Folder 1)
  - Agricultural Development Council, Inc. Volume XXI - Irrigation Policy and the Management of Irrigation Systems in Southeast Asia, 1976 (Box 232, Folder 2)
  - Agricultural Development Council, Inc. Volume XXII - The Economics of Tractors in South Asia - An Introduction to Agricultural Extension - Readings in Agricultural Administration, 1978; 1980 (Box 232, Folder 3)
  - Agricultural Development Council, Inc. Volume XXIII - Research and Teaching Forum - Staff Papers, 1977-1980 (Box 233, Folder 1)
  - Agricultural Development Council, Inc. Volume XXIV - Proceedings of Farm Management Teaching Workshop, 1977 (Box 233, Folder 2)
  - ADC - Papers and Reprints, 1970-1979 (Box 234, Folder 1)
  - ADC - Newsletter - 38. 39. 40, 1978-1979 (Box 234, Folder 2)
  - ADC - Staff Papers, 1977-1980 (Box 234, Folder 3)
  - ADC - Staff Papers, 1973-1976 (Box 235, Folder 1-3)
  - Papers - Workshop on Pre-Release Testing of Agricultural Technology, CIAT, Cali, Colombia, 1979 March 19-21 (Box 235, Folder 4)
  - Papers - Workshop on Pre-Release Testing of Agricultural Technology, CIAT, Cali, Colombia, 1979 March 19-21 (Box 236, Folder 1)
  - Papers - ADC-ICRISAT Conference - Adjustment Mechanism of Rural Labor Markets in Developing Areas, Patancheru, India, 1979 August 22-24 (Box 236, Folder 2-4)
  - Papers - ADC-ICRISAT Conference - Revised Hyderabad 1979 Papers, 1979 August 22-24 (Box 237, Folder 1-2)
  - Papers - Workshop on Research Methodology in the Study of Irrigation Organization, Fort Collins, CO, 1978 April 30-May 3 (Box 237, Folder 3-4)
  - Papers - Workshop on Research Methodology in the Study of Irrigation Organization, Fort Collins, CO, 1978 April 30-May 3 (Box 238, Folder 1)
  - Papers - Seminar on Cooperatives, Small Farmers and Development, Wingspread, WI, 1978 April 24-26 (Box 238, Folder 2-4)
  - Papers - Seminar on Cooperatives, Small Farmers and Development, Wingspread, WI, 1978 April 24-26 (Box 239, Folder 1)
  - A. T. Mosher - Monograph - Introduction to Agricultural Extension, 1976-1980 (Box 239, Folder 2)
  - J. Roumasset - Risk and Uncertainty Book, 1978-1980 (Box 239, Folder 3)
  - A. T. Mosher - Readings in Agricultural Administration - Correspondence and Permissions, 1979-1981 (Box 240, Folder 1)
  - A. T. Mosher - Readings in Agricultural Administration - Papers, 1970s (Box 240, Folder 2-3)
  - A. T. Mosher - Thinking About Rural Development, 1976 (Box 241, Folder 1)
  - A. T. Mosher - Resume of Rural Development Experience, 1977 (Box 241, Folder 2)
  - J. Wong - Group Farming in Asia Book - Singapore, 1977-1978 (Box 241, Folder 3)
  - Dorner - Cooperative and Commune - Group Farming in the Economic Development of Agriculture - Distribution, 1976-1977 (Box 241, Folder 4)
  - Interregional Publication (4 vols.) - Economic Theory, 1975-1976 (Box 241, Folder 5)
  - Binswanger and Ruttan - Induced Innovation: Technology, Institutions and Development, Johns Hopkins University Press, 1976-1978 (Box 241, Folder 6)
  - Stevenson - Graduate Study in the United States, 1975 (Box 242, Folder 1)
  - ADC-IRRI - Taylor-Wickham - Irrigation Policy and Management, 1977-1979 (Box 242, Folder 2)
  - Arndt, Dalrymple and Ruttan - Resource Allocation and Productivity in National and International Agricultural Research, 1976 (Box 242, Folder 3)
  - Man Land and Fish - Coastal Zone Management Book, 1979-1982 (Box 242, Folder 4)
  - H. P. Binswanger - The Economics of Tractors in Indian Subcontinent (Monograph), 1977-1980 (Box 242, Folder 5)
  - Lynch - Monograph - How to Make A Social Survey Interview Schedule - Instructions for Beginners (Box 243, Folder 1)
  - Penny - Hints for Research Works in the Social Sciences (Box 243, Folder 2)
  - Ong - Teaching Farm Management at the Undergraduate Level in U. S. Universities (Box 243, Folder 3)
  - Riley and Staatz - Food System Organization Problems in Developing Countries (Box 243, Folder 4)
  - Levine and Hart - Mobilizing Local Resources for Irrigation (Box 243, Folder 5)
  - Seminar Report - Communication Responsibilities in International Agricultural Research Centers (Box 243, Folder 6)
  - ADC Annual Report 1977 File (Box 244, Folder 1)
  - ADC Annual Report 1978 File (Box 244, Folder 2)
  - ADC Annual Report 1979 File (Box 244, Folder 3)
  - ADC Annual Report 1980 File (Box 244, Folder 4)
  - Hemmi and Atsumi - Mechanization of Small Scale Peasant Farming (Box 244, Folder 5)
  - Nelson - Food Aid and Development - Reprint (Box 244, Folder 6)
  - Nelson - Food Aid and Development - Monograph (Box 245, Folder 1)
  - Binswanger and Rosenzweig - Contractual Arrangements, Employment and Wages in Rural Labor Markets: A Critical Review (Box 245, Folder 2)
  - Langham - Importance of Bypassed Areas in Asian Economic Development (Box 245, Folder 3)
  - Newsletter, No. 41 (Box 246, Folder 1)
  - Seminar Report - Cooperatives, Small Farmers and Rural Development (Box 246, Folder 2)
  - Binswanger - Rural Household Studies in Asia - Manuscript (Box 246, Folder 3)
  - Binswanger - Rural Household Studies in Asia - Publication (Box 246, Folder 4)
  - Max Langham and Ralph Retzlaff - Agricultural Sector Analysis in Asia (Box 246, Folder 5)
  - Taylor - The Economics of Malaysian Paddy Production and Irrigation (Box 246, Folder 6)
- Personnel Files, 13; 5.58 Cubic Feet 6 letter document boxes and 7 legal document boxes
  - Former Trustees (Box 247, Folder 1)
    Restricted - Personnel
  - Mosher (Box 247, Folder 2)
  - A. F. McCormack (Box 247, Folder 3)
  - Mosher (Box 248, Folder 1)
  - McGinnis, Ada M. (Box 248, Folder 2)
  - Vernon W. Ruttan (Box 248, Folder 3)
  - Frances Pace (Box 248, Folder 4)
  - Judy C. Moore (Box 248, Folder 5)
  - Rosemary Amodeo (Box 248, Folder 6)
  - Dorothy Pafumi (Box 248, Folder 7)
  - Roumasset (Box 249, Folder 1)
  - Daisy Vazquez (Box 249, Folder 2)
  - Nancy E. Waxler (Box 249, Folder 3)
  - Swenson (Box 249, Folder 4)
  - Clay (Box 250, Folder 1)
  - Robert E. Evenson (Box 250, Folder 2)
  - William M. Bateson (Box 250, Folder 3)
  - Langham (Box 251, Folder 1)
  - John Duewel (Box 251, Folder 2)
  - Harlan Lampe (Box 251, Folder 3)
  - Harris, Jane (Box 251, Folder 4)
  - V. Ruttan (Box 252, Folder 1)
  - A. Russell Stevenson (Box 252, Folder 2)
  - Donald C. Taylor (Box 252, Folder 3)
  - Plath, C. Vinton (Box 252, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous Staff (Box 252, Folder 5)
  - Pray, Carl (Box 253, Folder 1)
  - Retzlaff (Box 253, Folder 2)
  - Taylor (Box 254, Folder 1)
  - Weisblat, A. M. (Box 254, Folder 2)
  - White, Benjamin (Box 255, Folder 1)
  - Collier, William L. (Box 255, Folder 2)
  - Shao-er Ong (Box 255, Folder 3)
  - Shao-er Ong (Box 256, Folder 1-2)
  - Collier, William L. (Box 257, Folder 1)
  - Burger, Viet (Box 257, Folder 2)
  - Binswanger, Hans (Box 258, Folder 1)
  - 1977 Trustee Program Review (Box 258, Folder 2)
  - McLean, Donald H. - Former Trustee (Box 258, Folder 3)
  - MacMillan, Whitney - Former Trustee (Box 258, Folder 4)
  - Presidential Search 1977 (Box 259, Folder 1)
  - John D. Rockefeller 3rd - Former Trustee (Box 259, Folder 2)
  - Wharton, C. R. Jr. - Former Trustee (Box 259, Folder 3)
- Financial records, 1953-1980; 14; 28.45 Cubic Feet 25 containers
  - Employee financial records (Box 260)
  - Employee financial records (Box 261)
  - Employee financial records (Box 262)
  - Cash Receipts, 1968-1979 (Box 263)
  - General Ledger Accounting Book, 1969-1978 (Box 263)
  - General Journal, 1977-1979 (Box 264)
  - Bangkok Cash Receipts and Cash Disbursements, 1976-1979 (Box 264)
  - Publications, 1972 (Box 265)
  - Publications, 1966-1975 (Box 265)
  - Securities Ledger, 1968-1980 (Box 266)
  - Associates - Closed Details, Work Budget, Salaries and Benefits, Advances, 1975-1980 (Box 266)
  - Payroll Journal, 1960s (Box 266)
  - Salaries Journal, 1959-1963 (Box 267)
  - Journal Entries (Box 267)
  - Auditors' reports (Box 268)
  - Auditors' reports (Box 269)
  - Work Papers - Trial Balances, 1976-1977 (Box 270)
  - Work Papers - Trial Balances, 1971-1973 (Box 271)
  - Work Papers - Trial Balances, 1975 (Box 272)
  - GIFTS - Ford Foundation Programs (Box 272)
  - International Crops Research Institute for the Semi-Arid Tropics (ICRISAT) - RTN Seminar Grant (Box 272)
  - Financial Statements, 1956-1962 (Box 273)
  - Financial Statements, 1971-1975 (Box 273)
  - Work Papers - Trial Balances, 1978 (Box 273)
  - Work Papers - Trial Balances, 1979 (Box 274)
  - Taxes - ADC Exempt Status, Bank Reconciliation (Box 275)
  - Bank Reconciliation (Box 275)
  - Grants Ledger (Box 277)
  - Cash Disbursements, 1965-1967 (Box 277)
  - General Ledger Accounting Book, 1959-1962 (Box 277)
  - General Ledger Accounting Book, 1963 July-December (Box 277)
  - Cash Receipts, Journal Expenditures, 1963 July-December (Box 277)
  - General Ledger Accounting Book, 1959 December-1963 July (Box 277)
  - General Ledger Accounting Book, 1953 December-1959 November (Box 277)
  - General Ledger Accounting Book, 1963 January-June (Box 278)
  - General Ledger Accounting Book, 1953-1956 (Box 278)
  - Cash Expenditures and Disbursements, 1964-1968 (Box 278)
  - Cash Disbursement Journals, 1963-1966 (Box 278)
  - General Ledger Accounting Book, 1955-1957 (Box 278)
  - Cash Receipts - Cash Disbursements, 1963 June-July (Box 279)